Now instead of kicking with the front leg, we're going to go into back leg round house kick.
it's a little different move front and we're going to show that right now so we're going to use the back leg o.k.
this is now our front leg, this is our back leg.
we're kicking with the back.
As you step, the front leg has to pivot.
that way you don't hurt your knee, now the back leg is set up for that kick.
You have to use your hips, the whole body rotates into that bag so the pivoting on that foot o.k.
One more time.
So you take the front leg, step over to the side.
also think that this is a person with arms and legs, you want to get out of the way so he can't hit you o.k.